Guide to the Radio TV Services Records, circa 1937 - 2008
Duke University. University Archives
- Sound Recordings, 1960-1988 and undated
  - Reel-to-Reel Tapes, 1960-1975, undated
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. C. G. Brookhout on the expansion of the Duke Marine Lab, Mar. 2, 1966 (Reel B-437)
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. Robert Menzies on the Peru Expedition, Mar. 3, 1966 (Reel B-441-A)
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. Robert Menzies on the Peru Expedition, Mar. 3, 1966 (Reel B-441-B)
    - Interview with Mr. Reynolds Price on writing for WPTF, Mar. 7, 1966 (Reel B-442)
    - Dr. Herbert Aptheker Speech in Page Auditorium, Mar. 8, 1966 (Reel B-446)
    - Dr. Herbert Aptheker Question and Answer Period, Mar. 8, 1966 (Reel B-447)
    - Speech by Mr. Malcolm Cowley on The Genius and Talent of William Faulkner, Mar. 38 [sic], 1966 (Reel B-471)
    - National Fencing Championships: Two Interviews with John LeBar for WPTF, Mar. 1966 (Reel B-481)
    - Selected Sculpture and Decorative Art: Brummer Collection, May 6, 1967 (Reel B-482-A)
    - Selected Sculpture and Decorative Art: Brummer Collection, May 6, 1967 (Reel B-482-B)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight at Newcomen Society Dinner, Apr. 18, 1966 (Reel B-487)
    - Oceanography: Interview: Dr. B. C. Heezen on his oceanographic discovery on Eastward, Mar. 30, 1966 (Reel B-490)
    - Richard Nixon: Press Conference Duke University Law Day, Apr. 30, 1966. (Reel B-494)
      - A CD reference copy of this recording has been made. Data file masters also exist for this recording.
    - Dr. Arthur A. Lawson: Student sponsored speech on Viet Nam, Apr. 19, 1966 (Reel B-497-A)
    - Oceanography: Two interviews: Dr. Orin Pilkey, Mr. George Newton, May 6, 1966, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel B-503)
    - Dean Miller's Address: 30th Reunion, Jan. 29, 1966, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel B-504)
    - Annual Meeting Law School Alumni Assoc., Apr. 30, 1966 (Reel B-505)
    - Oceanography: Interviews with Dr. Orin Pilkey and George Newton, May 1966 (Reel B-507)
    - Sound effect of a frog, Duke Gardens, May 1966 (Reel B-509)
    - Lecture given by Chief Justice Charles S. Desmond, May 13, 1966 (Reel B-510-A)
    - Interview: Mr. A. Loy Nash on Barber Writes a Book for Margaret Brickell WPTF, May 17, 1966 (Reel B-516)
    - Commencement: Interview with James F. Webb, Dr. Townes, June 6, 1966 (Reel B-519)
    - Report to Board of Trustees by Dr. Douglas M. Knight, June 1966, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel B-522)
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Mr. Joe Tally, Dr. Theodore Ropp, June 4, 1966 (Reel B-524-A)
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Mr. Joe Tally, Dr. Theodore Ropp, June 4, 1966 (Reel B-524-A)
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Dr. Calvin Hoover and Question Period, June 4, 1966 (Reel B-524-B)
    - Graduation Exercises: Address by Dr. Charles H. Townes, June 1966 (Reel B-525)
    - Dean Robert Cushman's comments on The Vatican Council, June 1966 (Reel B-527)
    - Interview: Dean Robert Cushman on II Vatican Council, June 21, 1966 (Reel B-531)
    - Interview with Dr. E. R. Latty on Trends and Changes in Law, Sept. 1966 (Box 8, Reel B-569)
    - Speech by Bishop Pike, Oct. 11, 1966 (Reel B-582-A)
    - Speech by Bishop Pike, Oct. 11, 1966 (Reel B-582-B)
    - News Conference with Bishop Pike, Oct. 10, 1966 (Reel B-583)
    - Dr. Walter Nielsen: Retirement Dinner in his honor, Oct. 7, 1966 (Reel B-584)
    - National Academy of Sciences Dinner/Address by Dr. Knight, Oct. 18, 1966 (Reel B-590)
    - National Academy of Science Major Address by Dr. Weinburg, Oct. 17, 1966 (Reel B-600-A)
    - National Academy of Science Major Address by Dr. Weinburg, Oct. 17, 1966 (Reel B-600-B)
    - Ceremony to name the Duke University Library The William R. Perkins Library, Dec. 11, 1966 (Reel B-602)
    - Durham welcomes Dr. Douglas M. Knight, Sept. 19, 1963 (Reel B-603)
    - Campus Club Meeting, Feb. 8, 1967 (Reel B-606)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Justice Byron R. White, Mar. 6, 1967 (Reel B-607)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Stokely Carmichael, Apr. 1967 (Reel B-608-A)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Stokely Carmichael, Apr. 1967 (Reel B-608-B)
    - Student Union: Mr. Christopher Craft, May 9, 1967 (Reel B-609-A)
    - Student Union: Mr. Christopher Craft, May 9, 1967 (Reel B-609-B)
    - Remarks by Dr. Knight to Board of Trustees, Mar. 4, 1967-Mar. 5, 1967 (Reel B-613)
    - President Knight's speech to Executive Committee, Sept. 25, 1964 (Reel B-614)
    - Interview with Dr. Kenneth Clark on the International Greek New Testament Project, July 1967 (Reel B-616-A)
    - Interview with Dr. Kenneth Clark on the International Greek New Testament Project, July 1967 (Reel B-616-B)
    - Special Report fed to CBS by John Van Hecke: Dr. Knight's comments on the public housing in Durham, N.C., July 27, 1967 (Reel B-617)
    - Dedication of Wallace Wade Stadium, July 27, 1967 (Reel B-618)
    - News Conference: Dr. Knight's comments to the news media concerning the public housing situation in Durham, N. C., July 27, 1967 (Reel B-619)
    - North Carolina News Conference: Guest Speaker Dr. Douglas Knight, July 31, 1967 (Reel B-620)
    - Dr. Knight: Meeting of the Board of Trustees Evening Session, Nov. 1964 (Reel B-621-A)
    - Dr. Knight: Meeting of the Board of Trustees Evening Session, Nov. 1964 (Reel B-621-B)
    - Dr. Knight's Report to the Board of Trustees, June 3, 1967 (Reel B-626)
    - Duke University Convocation, Provost Taylor Cole presiding, Sept. 20, 1967 (Reel B-629-A)
    - Duke University Convocation, Sept. 29, 1967 (Reel B-629-B)
    - Phone interviews with Howard, Tipton, Wilkinson, Prothro, all paying tribute to Coach Wallace Wade, Oct. 1967 (Reel B-630)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Norman Cousins, Oct. 12, 1967 (Reel B-631)
    - Mr. George V. Allen's speech to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, Dec. 1967 (Reel B-632)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's speech to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, Jan. 8, 1968 (Reel B-633)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Gerald Ford speaking in U. S. Economic Policy, Feb. 2, 1968 (Reel B-634)
    - Dr. Knight's Report to the Faculty, Mar. 21, 1968 (Reel B-635)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Sidney Cohen speaking on LSD, Mar. 18, 1968 (Reel B-637-A)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Sidney Cohen speaking on LSD, Mar. 18, 1968 (Box 9, Reel B-637-B)
    - Duke University Service for Peace in Duke Chapel, Apr. 3, 1968 (Reel B-638)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Dr. Adam Clayton Powell, Apr. 1, 1968 (Reel B-639-A)
    - Mr. Charles B. Wade, Jr.: Who Will be the Next Mr. Duke?, Dec. 10, 1967 (Reel B-640)
    - Oceanography: Interview on Board the Eastward, Nov. 1967 (Reel B-641)
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Reel B-643-A)
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Reel B-643-B)
    - Memorial Service at Duke Chapel for Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr., Apr. 6, 1968 (Reel B-643-C)
    - Statement by Mr. Wright Tisdale to students in Silent Vigil, Apr. 10, 1968 (Reel B-644)
    - North Carolina News Conference featuring Miss Bunny Small on the Silent Vigil, Apr. 22, 1968 (Reel B-645)
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. John Vernberg on A Barrier in the Sea, Mar. 6, 1968 (Reel B-646-A)
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. John Vernberg on the I.B.P. Program, Mar. 6, 1968 (Reel B-646-B)
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. Ralph Brauer on his experiments at the lab, Mar. 6, 1968 (Reel B-647-A)
    - Oceanography: Interview with Dr. Ralph Brauer on Hydra I, Mar. 6, 1968 (Reel B-647-B)
    - Oceanography: News Conference with Dr. Ralph Brauer on Hydra I, May 3, 1968 (Reel B-648)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Mr. Ramsey Clark, U.S. Attorney General, May 8, 1968 (Reel B-649)
    - Duke Homestead Ceremonies, Apr. 28, 1968 (Reel B-650)
    - Dedication of the Duke Phytotron, May 10, 1968 (Reel B-651)
    - Wallace Wade Day Dinner honoring Coach Wade, Great Hall, Sept. 1967 (Reel B-652-A)
    - Wallace Wade Day Dinner honoring Coach Wade, Great Hall, Sept. 1967 (Reel B-652-B)
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Reel B-653-A)
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Reel B-653-B)
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Reel B-653-C)
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Reel B-653-D)
    - Greensboro Alumni Association Meeting: Remarks by Mr. Ashmore, Mr. Ross, Apr. 24, 1968 (Reel B-653-E)
    - Interview with Mrs. Mildred Hendrix on the Duke Chapel organ, Jan. 1968 (Reel B-654-A)
    - Interview with Mrs. Mildred Hendrix on the Duke Chapel organ, Jan. 1968 (Reel B-654-B)
    - Duke University Organ recital, June 3, 1968 (Reel B-655)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Reel B-656-A)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Reel B-656-B)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Rev. Malcolm Boyd, Feb. 12, 1968 (Reel B-656-C)
    - Baccalaureate Service Duke Chapel, June 2, 1968 (Reel B-657)
    - Commencement Exercises: Dr. Barnes Woodhall, June 1968 (Reel B-658)
    - Joint News Conference: Dr. Albert Whiting, Pres N.C. College, and Dr. R. Taylor Cole, Provost Duke University, July 17, 1968 (Reel B-659)
    - Discussion about the Duke Chapel organ, July 1968 (Reel B-660)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Reel B-661-A)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Box 10, Reel B-661-B)
    - Student Union Major Speaker: Ambassador George C. McGhee, Sept. 24, 1968 (Reel B-661-C)
    - News Conference with Mr. James Gardner held at Duke University Law School, Apr. 29, 1969 (Reel B-662)
    - Dr. Clark Kerr's address in Page Aud., Nov. 18, 1968 (Reel B-664)
    - Student Activism: Interview with 3 students about Silent Vigil at Duke, Apr. 10, 1968 (Reel B-665)
    - Student Activism: Mr. Clarence Whitefield's address to Kiwanis Club on student unrest, Mar. 3, 1968 (Reel B-666-A)
    - Student Activism: Mr. Clarence Whitefield's address to Kiwanis Club on student unrest, Mar. 3, 1968 (Reel B-666-B)
    - Student Activism: Alan Kerckhoff speaking in Page Auditorium on student unrest, Feb. 16, 1969 (Reel B-667-A)
    - Student Activism: Alan Kerckhoff speaking in Page Auditorium on student unrest, Feb. 16, 1969 (Reel B-667-B)
    - Student Activism: Comments at Univ. House by Dr. Knight and members of student body, Feb. 15, 1969 (Reel B-668)
    - Student Activism: Dr. Douglas Knight's appearance on N.C. News Conf., Oct. 14, 1968 (Reel B-669)
    - Student Activism: Development Dinner-Raleigh, N.C. Q&A portion-Mr. Charles B. Wade, Apr. 1969 (Reel B-670)
    - Convocation: Dr. Douglas Knight, Sept. 18, 1968 (Reel B-673-A)
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Reel B-674-A)
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Reel B-674-B)
    - Mr. Michael Harrington speaking in Page Aud., Oct. 15, 1968 (Reel B-674-C)
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Reel B-676-A)
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Reel B-676-B)
    - Dr. Knight: Board of Trustees Meeting, Mar. 7, 1969 (Reel B-676-C)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Academic Council Meeting, Dec. 19, 1968 (Reel B-677-A)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Academic Council Meeting, Dec. 19, 1968 (Reel B-677-B)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Executive Committee-Trustee Meeting, Dec. 7, 1968 (Reel B-681-A)
    - Dr. Douglas Knight's address to Executive Committee-Trustee Meeting, Dec. 7, 1968 (Reel B-681-B)
    - Board of Trustees: Reports from Dean Pye, Dr. Knight, Mr. Huestis, Mar. 28, 1969 (Reel B-683)
    - Commencement: Hon. Angier Biddle Duke's Address, June 2, 1969 (Reel B-684-A)
    - Commencement: Hon. Angier Biddle Duke's Address, June 2, 1969 (Reel B-684-B)
    - Baccalaureate: Dr. Knight delivers final sermon, June 1, 1969 (Reel B-685)
    - The Office of President: Interview with Dr. Knight, Apr. 1969 (Reel B-686-A)
    - The Office of President: Interview with Dr. Knight, Apr. 1969 (Reel B-686-B)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 31, 1969 (Reel B-697-A)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 31, 1969 (Reel B-697-B)
    - Convocation: Dr. Woodhall and Dr. Hobbs, Sept. 25, 1969 (Reel B-688)
    - Mr. Howard Fuller: Speech at beginning of Black Week, Feb. 15, 1970 (Reel B-702)
    - Impression of Campus unrest by Mr. Charles Braswell, 1969 (Reel B-705)
    - President Sanford: Strike Day Activities, May 6, 1970 (Reel B-709)
    - President Sanford: Duke Blue Devil Club Breakfast, Aug. 4, 1970 (Reel B-710)
    - Terry Sanford: N.C. News Conference, Sept. 14, 1970 (Box 11, Reel B-711)
    - Terry Sanford: Inauguration Ceremonies, Oct. 18, 1970 (Reel B-712)
    - Major Speakers Series: Senator George McGovern, Oct. 18, 1970 (Reel B-713)
    - Terry Sanford speaks to the Rotary and Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club, May 18, 1970 (Reel B-714)
    - A. Kenneth Pye talks to the Tobaccoland Kiwanis Club on Law Day, 1970 (Reel B-715)
    - News Conference: Introducing Mike McGee as new Duke football coach, undated (Reel B-716)
    - Alumni Lecture Series: Duke in the 70's, undated (Reel B-722)
    - Dedication of the A. Hollis Edens Residence Halls, May 2, 1970 (Reel B-723)
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, May 23, 1971 (Reel B-724)
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, June 6, 1971 (Reel B-725)
    - Protestant Hour: Duke Chapel Choir, June 20, 1971 (Reel B-726)
    - Presentation Ceremony: Codex Vaticanus to Rare Book Room Perkins Library, Sept. 24, 1971 (Reel B-727)
    - Eddie Cameron comments on Old Football Film of Duke games: Talk to Durham Kiwanis Club, undated (Reel B-728)
    - Testimonial Dinner for Dean Robert E. Cushman, May 24, 1971 (Reel B-729)
    - Retirement Dinner for Eddie Cameron, 1972 (Reel B-730)
    - Retirement Dinner for Dr. Joseph Spengler, Prof. of Economics, 1972 (Reel B-731)
    - Commencement, 1972 (Reel B-732)
    - Commencement, 1973 (Reel B-735)
    - Major Speakers Series: Ms. Gloria Steinem and Dr. Greshem, Spring 1973 (Reel B-736)
    - Sanford meets with Triangle Mayors to offer Duke resources, Sept. 19, 1972 (Reel B-737)
    - Founder's Day Service in Chapel with Sanford, undated (Reel B-738)
    - Mitch Mitchell talks about history of southern tenant farmers and general labor and farm problems, undated (Reel B-739)
    - Dr. H. Shelton Smith talks about the church's role in the development of racism, Jan. 10, 1970 (Reel B-740)
    - Ms. Betty Friedan presents a Major Speakers lecture, Jan. 26, 1973 (Reel B-741-A)
    - Ms. Betty Friedan presents a Major Speakers lecture, Jan. 26, 1973 (Reel B-741-B)
    - B. F. Skinner presents a Major Speakers lecture, Fall 1972 (Reel B-742-A)
    - B. F. Skinner presents a Major Speakers lecture, Fall 1972 (Reel B-742-B)
    - Sen. Sam Ervin speaks to the Duke Law Forum, Spring 1973 (Reel B-745)
    - N.C. Sen Sam Ervin talks to N.C. Press-Duke Dinner, Jan. 1973, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel B-745)
    - Epoch Campaign Announcement: Sanford, Jones, McMahon, Fall 1973 (Reel B-746)
    - Terry Sanford's first news conference as Duke President, undated (Reel B-747)
    - Sanford announces candidacy for U.S. president, Spring 1973 (Reel B-748)
    - Alex Haley, Spring 1973 (Reel B-749)
    - Alex Haley, Spring 1973 (Reel B-750)
    - Impeachment rally on main quad, Fall 1973 (Reel B-751)
    - Press Association Annual Meeting, Jan. 1974 (Reel B-752)
    - Open Forum on student and campus related topics, Spring 1967 (Reel B-754)
    - Open Forum on student and campus related topics, Spring 1967 (Reel B-755)
    - Duke Major Speakers: Sander Vanocur, Spring 1973 (Box 12, Reel B-756)
    - Stewart Udall predicts about energy crisis, Fall 1973 (Reel B-757)
    - Tom Wolfe, author, speaks on youth, Fall 1973 (Reel B-758)
    - Interview with Dr. Frank Slaughter, author, Fall 1973 (Reel B-759)
    - Duke Major Speakers: Buckminster Fuller, Fall 1973 (Reel B-760)
    - Duke Major Speakers: Buckminster Fuller, Fall 1973 (Reel B-761)
    - Sanford's Inauguration as Duke President, undated (Reel B-763)
    - Dan Rather's speech at Duke University, Jan. 1974 (Reel B-764)
    - Press conference held to announce the finding of the Monitor by Duke University and other researchers, Mar. 7, 1974 (Reel B-765-A)
    - Press conference held to announce the finding of the Monitor by Duke University and other researchers, Mar. 7, 1974 (Reel B-765-B)
    - Interview with John Newton, discoverer of the ship, the Monitor, Mar. 1974 (Reel B-766)
    - News conference with John Newton and others, conducted on board press boat at sea, undated (Reel B-767)
    - Commencement: Trudeau, Robinson, Martin, 1974 (Reel B-768)
    - Cesar Chavez speaking at Duke, Sept. 11, 1974 (Reel B-770)
    - Durham Forum, Oct. 20, 1974 (Reel B-771)
    - Clarence Kelly, FBI Director, speaking at Duke, Dec. 4, 1974 (Reel B-772)
    - Milton Friedman speaking at Duke, Jan. 24, 1975 (Reel B-773)
    - Student World Day of Prayer, Vietnam Era, Bill Patton, undated (Reel No number)
    - Monitor: Interview with John Newton, Mar. 7, 1974 (Reel No number)
    - Study-in, Mar. 1, 1963 (Reel No number)
    - Dr. Hart, Dr. Knight: Speeches to Board of Trustees, Nov. 13, 1967 (Reel No number)
    - Wild Track: James B. Duke Prof. teaching class, scene 32B, undated (Reel No number)
    - Founder's Day Dinner: Knight, Tisdale, and Perkins, 1964 (Reel No number)
    - King #1, undated (Reel No number)
    - King #2, undated (Reel No number)
    - Duke 140-narration, undated (Reel No number)
    - Ceremony to name the Duke Univ. Library the William R. Perkins Library, Dec. 11, 1966 (Reel No number)
    - The Duke Story, June 26, 1965 (Reel No number)
    - The Duke Story: Interview-Dr. Knight in his office, undated (Reel No number)
    - Founder's Day: Christine Mims, Dec. 3, 1972 (Reel No number)
    - Founder's Day, 1962 (Reel No number)
    - Founder's Day: LaPrade, undated (Reel No number)
    - Ashmore explaining Vigil to staff, undated, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel No number)
    - Study-in, Nov. 13, 1967, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel No number)
    - Knight and Cockschutt, June 4, 1969, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel No number)
    - Introduction of Guest Speaker by Dr. Bisell, Address by Dr. Knight, President Duke Univ. Scarborough College, Toronto, Oct. 4, 1966, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel No number)
    - Betty Friedan, undated, 1 sound reel: 5 inch, 1/4 inch. (Reel No number)
- Film and Video circa 1937-1987 and undated
  Original recordings are closed to use. Digitized copies are available for some recordings. Please contact University Archives staff for more information.
  - Film, C and D series 1951-1974, undated
    All film in this series is 16mm. The film is stored on a variety of different sized reels and in different sized cans. Sometimes the film is in a can without a reel, sometimes without a core.
    Individuals related to Duke include Terry Sanford, Douglas M. Knight, Wright Tisdale, George Allen, Orin Pilkey, and Robert Menzies. In addition to numerous campus scenes, there is footage of the Duke Marine Lab, the ship Eastward, convocation, football from the 1950s, the discovery of the U.S.S. Monitor, the Epoch Campaign announcement, and outtakes from the film This is Duke.
    This series is indexed by title and by subject in the card file index in Box 3.
    The films in this series were originally numbered C-1 through C-164 and D-1 through D-8. That arrangement has been retained here. A number of unnumbered reels were received by the archives in the same boxes as these films and seem to belong in this series. Films without numbers are listed at the end of the series, arranged in alphabetical order by title.
    - Dedication Dates are set for Duke's new Law School Bldg., Apr. 26, 1963-Apr. 27, 1963, 2 film reels: 3 inch, in 7 inch can. (Box 13, Reel C-1)
    - Aerial Shots of Football Stadium, Sept. 24, 1963, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-2)
    - unlabeled, undated, 1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-7)
    - Marine Lab Aerials, 1963, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-11)
    - Eastward Launching: Original Color & Outtakes, undated, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-22)
    - Aerial Survey, Oct. 1964, 2 film reels: 3 inch, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-23)
      One reel is labeled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of Duke Forest and West Campus, B&W-Orig. PxR.
      The other is lableled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of Duke Forest. Also shots of plane, Orig. Rev. B&W.
    - Eastward's First Cruise: TV release, 1 min., Ship leaving port, Dr. Menzies, Dr. Bonhout, Nov. 1964, 1 film reel (1 min.): 3 inch, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-25)
    - Eastward: B&W Prints, Nov. 3, 1964, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-25)
    - Aerial Survey II, Oct. 1964, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-26)
      Reel is labeled: Campus Scenes. Aerial view of W Campus (shaky), Flying at chapel, Color workprint-Ink edge nos.
    - Convocation, 1964, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-28)
    - Campus Scenes, undated, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-29)
    - Eastward 800 ft. Rev. Orig. Apr. 1965 1 Rev. w/print with ink edge nos. Also, Kenneth Galbraith, 1 film on core, no reel, in 10-inch can. (Reel C-46)
    - Regional Center for the Study of Aging (Used by Peggy Mann Show): Dr. Eisdorfer, Mar. 26, 1965, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-51)
    - Fund Raising, Fifth Decade Campaign Announcement: Dr. Knight, Wright Tisdale, George Allen, June 9, 1965, 1 film reel: 7 inch. (Reel C-53)
    - Response to Our Challenge, May 23, 1966, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-89)
    - TV Feature: Deep Sea Mineral Deposits, Dr. Orin Pilkey, May 1966, 1 film reel: 7 inch. (Reel C-95)
    - Eastward Launching, A Roll, Sept. 1964, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-100)
    - Eastward Launching, B Roll, Sept. 1964, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-100)
    - Oceanography, A Roll, Jan. 27, 1965, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Box 14, Reel C-101)
    - Oceanography, B Roll, Jan. 27, 1965, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-101)
    - Campaign Announcement: Original, Outtakes, June 1966, 1 film on core, no reel, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-124)
    - Eastward Cruise: Dr. Orin Pilkey, June 1966, 1 film reel: 3 inch. in 7-inch can. (Reel C-129)
      Note on reel: Orig. Rev. Mag. stripe/silent.
    - Football: Duke - Navy Sports Film with Sound undated, 1 film on core in 10-inch can. (Box 22, Reel C-130)
    - Blacks Seize Allen Building, Feb. 13, 1969, 1 film reel: si., b&w; 3 inch, in 7-inch can. (Box 14, Reel C-136)
      Note on can: Pictures began approx 4:30 p.m. -Police and Tear Gas- B&W Original
      Reference Copy: VHS. UA88-57-13
      Reference Copy: DVD. UA88-57-13
    - Original color Eastward outtakes, 1967, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-142)
    - Dr. Menzies of Duke on a section of Dead Sea off N. C. Coast, Jan. 23, 1967, 1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-142)
    - Dr. Menzies of Duke on new Panama Canal Problems, Jan. 24, 1967, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-143)
    - Duke Marine Lab, Beaufort: Research, Limnoria, Dr. R. Menzies, 1967, 1 film reel: 3 inch, in 7-inch can. (Reel C-144)
    - Campus Scenes, undated, 1 film, no reel, no core, in 7 inch can. (Reel C-146)
      Note on can:
      1. Girls in bedroom
      2. Boy in arch
      3. Doctor & Nurse
      4. Old Classroom Shots
      5. Shots of Chapel
      6. The End Electron Microscope
      7. Campus Shots